Hey, how's it going guys? It is John here with another video ad tutorial.
I'm gonna be a little quiet on this one just because my kids are sleeping right
over there. But, um,
today we're gonna be talking about YouTube ads and how to crack YouTube ads.
It's not easy. It's, um, it takes a, a particular formula.
You know,
things that work on Facebook on TikTok aren't going to convert on YouTube
just because the mindset is different for YouTube and people
aren't there to necessarily buy, they're there to be entertained and to learn.
So you almost have to, um, recreate that environment for,
for the end user. And so in this video, um,
it is the same brand that, um, I've shared in the past,
but it is the leakproof underwear brand. Um,
and over here I have the actual script breakdown. Uh,
this is the actual video. We've tested a ton of videos.
This is just one of them, one of many, but this one got 1.78 million views.
So we were actually able to scale this ad,
and basically what happened was we kept hitting compliance issues.
So we had to kind of like gut the video and try to take out all these like,
trigger keywords. But, you know, we had, we had launched this video a few times.
We had run it for, for over a year, um, with, with a lot of success.
But moving into the overall kind of concept
here, um, I tested YouTube, um,
in the past and just didn't get any results. And the reason was, um,
was because I wasn't like formatting the videos, right?
I wasn't scripting the videos, right? I wasn't, um,
really understanding how like a, a winning V ss l works on YouTube.
And I actually came across this, uh, really awesome affiliate course that, uh,
that I got for very, I pretty much got for free,
but they broke down some of the top affiliate offers on YouTube.
And this was the, like, the biggest light bulb for me. Um,
when I saw the structure and the,
the videos that were being scaled on YouTube to like the twenties of millions,
no one was really applying this to e-comm.
And I still don't feel like people are applying this to e-comm. And there,
there's a huge opportunity there and, and mean this could be applied to any,
any type of offer. But, um,
I'm gonna break down the actual sequence here and then the timeline. So,
and I'll, and I'll share with you like the reason why we did these things.
So I'll play, I don't want, we, we don't have to play the whole video,
but woman who spend, I'll share, you know,
I'll share the video as we go and I'll talk about it.
But I'll just go over this script really quick. Um,
so over here is the sequence. Uh,
this is why this is kind of just like my notes on like why this sequence is
important. I did a little screenshot and then the actual script here. All right,
so let's just break down this, this pattern interrupt, um,
or scroll stopper, whatever you wanna call it.
Woman who spends hundreds on disposable diapers and panta aligners finds a
solution to a leaky bladder issue. If you're
Okay, boom, right there. That is the, the scroll stopper.
This is the hook. Um,
there's a visual and there's an audio and there's text, right?
The first thing that you see. So the problem with this,
the problem that the customers face with this particular product is
they rely on diapers and pads to stop their leaks.
And obviously that's a very expensive, and it's a very uncomfortable solution.
And so we wanted to really address that from the beginning. Um,
and this visual right here,
showing the diapers plus money is a visual demonstration of like,
okay, I know that that looks familiar to me. I know what that is,
and obviously I know I spend money on this, right?
So that is an alone, a really good hook. Um,
and then we show the, the solution here,
but we don't ever call out the solution until later.
That's the key thing with these YouTube ads is like, um,
you always want to keep this curiosity loop, right?
So the whole concept here,
the woman who spends hundreds of dollars on disposable diaper and pantyliners
finds a solution to her leaky bladder issue, right?
This is a curiosity loop. We, there's like, we're,
we're creating like this subject that, oh, who is this person and why? You know,
that's what we want to trigger in their minds.
So that's basically how this hook started. And, um, you know,
in future videos you can see like we basically just swapped out this shot,
um, with a different visual,
and then we can con we continued the ad to run when it starts to fatigue.
A woman who spends hundreds on disposable diapers and pan aligners finds a
solution to a leaky bladder issue, it,
Alright?
So another thing too that works really well on YouTube is
the fact that I shot this on an iPhone, okay?
This wasn't like professionally shot at all,
and I'm keeping the same aspect ratio here, uh,
nine by 16 in a, you know, 16 by nine format. And like, that's the thing.
It's like, it's not pretty. This, this video is not pretty whatsoever.
Like I didn't really take the time to make it very, you know, aesthetic.
It, it, it, it comes down to the content, comes down to the script,
comes down to the, the sequencing, all right?
That's really the power of YouTube and, you know, uh,
quality isn't as important for, for those who,
who really care about it. Um, so moving forward,
Leaky bladder issue,
if you're over 35 and experienced embarrassing leaks from loss of bladder
control and they're fed up with uncomfortable and expensive disposable
solutions, then you need to watch this.
Alright? So this is a very important section, alright? Um,
this is what is in it for them.
This is what's gonna get them to continue to watch. Okay?
So you have the hook pattern interrupt,
and then you have what's in it for them.
So you wanna make sure they don't click that next skip add button, right?
You have like less than 10 seconds or 15 seconds or so, um,
for them to, to skip. Uh, don't quote me on that, I forget what it is.
But this, this is a big qualifier, right?
So you want to add curiosity about the pain points and go against what they
already know.
If you're 35 and experience embarrassing leaks from loss of bladder control,
boom, pain point,
and are fed up with uncomfortable and expensive disposable solutions,
another pain point thinking that those are the only solutions out there,
then you need to watch this. Okay? So again,
we have this open curiosity loop and we're just continually kind of
subconsciously telling them, Hey, there's a problem here and we,
there could be a solution, but we're not gonna tell you what it is, right,
right away. Okay? So moving on to sequence number three,
the
Bladder issue.
If you're over 35 and experienced embarrassing leaks from loss of bladder
control and are fed up with uncomfortable and expensive disposable solutions,
then you need to watch this. Alright,
We ready to watch that? Sorry. This
A recent breakthrough in women's underwear technology demonstrated 90,
sorry,
a recent breakthrough in women's underwear technology demonstrated 96% better
coverage from urine, blood,
and sweat compared to traditional panties without relying on bulky,
uncomfortable pads or adult diapers.
Okay? Very chunky, very chunky, um, section right here,
but very, very, very important. Okay,
here we are talking about the new opportunity. Okay?
So I think this is a very, um,
very important one that a lot of people don't talk about, um,
in the e-com space,
but there's a solution to your pain and it's a fast and easy solution,
and it doesn't matter what your background is. Um, this makes,
you wanna keep watching to learn more of what this is. Okay?
So how we position this,
a recent breakthrough in women's underwear technology demonstrates
96% better coverage compared to traditional panties without relying on
bulky and uncomfortable pads or adult diapers, right? This is,
um, this is really important because right here we,
we still have that curiosity loop happening, right? A recent breakthrough.
I think the best affiliates and the best marketers in the world are using
some sort of mechanism, um,
some sort of proprietary technology that's like
kind of the vehicle of why their product is, is, is the best,
is the best solution. Watch, let's watch it one more time.
A recent breakthrough in women,
And I'm gonna do, that's
A recent breakthrough in women's underwear technology demonstrated 96% better
coverage from urine, blood, and sweat compared to traditional panties with,
All right? So from a visual standpoint, um, I'm just,
I'm just going hard on the, on the demos, I'm going hard on the,
on the visuals here. One thing that we learned is like, you know, we,
we want to make a really strong argument here. Hold on. All right, I'm back. Um,
I forgot to even talk about the visuals, but, uh, let's go back in a second.
So here we really wanna show off the, the demonstrations here.
Like this is one of the most powerful things if you can demonstrate the product
and use, you know, over and over and over again, it creates a really,
really strong argument. And, um, going back to,
to this shot right here. So after you know, the, the initial hook,
this demonstration, very, very powerful woman peeing herself.
Lots of split screens. You're gonna notice that I use a lot of split screens,
um, just because I'm taking up more real estate on screen and I'm,
it's more opportunity to capture the person,
capture the viewer's attention visually. Um,
like I'm throwing a lot of different things at the screen.
Sing leaks from loss of bladder control and they're fed up
And yeah, so these are all just shot on iPhone. Very simple.
We're not trying to overcomplicate it,
but going back to this demonstration,
like we're showing the product in use, right? We're,
we're really trying to make an argument here at the end of the day,
Additional panties.
And so yeah, this is that, that before and after, uh,
shot of traditional panties versus this one.
Meanwhile also talking about this breakthrough. What is this breakthrough,
right? We haven't even mentioned the product. Okay,
now we move on to the next sequence, which is devalue perception.
Relying on bulky uncomfortable pads or adult diapers.
Design comforts leakproof panties were designed specifically for women who want
peace of mind protection and maximum comfort from urine leaks, blood and sweat,
click.
Alright, fantastic.
So once we've established that new opportunity,
now we're introducing the product. Okay? Um, design comforts,
leakproof panties were designed specifically for women who want peace of mind
protection, maximum comfort from urine, leak, explode, and sweat. All right?
So there's a lot jam packed in that copy right there. Um,
we're trying to hit those, those pain points, those key words that, you know,
the consumer wants to hear already. Peace of mind protection,
comfort leaks, blood and sweat.
These are all the keywords that they're already thinking about in their
mind and that they know. Okay? So from that copy perspective, you know,
we want to include that in the script. Now, from a visual perspective, again,
I'm using split screens here to one on the left show the demonstration.
I'm, I'm actually like, 'cause this is,
if I can hammer that home that this thing actually works, then we've got,
you know, we've, we've covering our bases from a, from an argument standpoint,
panties, and then a piece of, you know, showing it in use. We have the,
the model wearing it. Um, mind
Protection and maximum comfort from urine leaks,
Another leaking demo,
Blood and sweat click.
And, and as you can tell, like I'm, I'm dropping clips in here,
just kind of like as is I'm leaving that black border around there.
I'm not making it perfect.
And I think that's what kind of makes these videos stand out more is because
they like, they, they look way more like raw, right?
They're not super branded, they're not very commercially and it, you know,
gives you a reason to keep watching it. Um, versus like, you know, typical,
typical commercial, you're like, okay, I know this is an ad,
I know this is a commercial, I'm over it. I want to skip, even if it's like,
you know, produced super, super, super well. Um,
there's just that part of you that's like, okay,
I know I'm being sold right now, so moving on.
Um, and by the way, these are some of the ads Orx overlays.
This is like the check, check mark and cross mark. I love these, these,
I use 'em all the time.
What click shop now to,
Alright, so next we have our first C T a. Okay,
Click shop now to grab yourself a pair of these incredible leakproof underwear
Under. Alright, so this is actually another, um,
this is an end screen azer X end screen, uh, with Azer X arrow.
So you can definitely use that here. But right here on that C T A,
we are adding the offer, um, in a call to action, right?
So one important thing about YouTube is really just like
directing people where to go. So, you know,
we have the arrow on the left side, so that's where the,
the call to action's gonna be. So we wanna make that very clear.
And I think like if you don't,
if you don't add call to actions in your YouTube ads, you're gonna miss out. Um,
definitely something you, you need to include in your, in your content.
Um, so next thing, so yeah, basically let this,
you want to give the opportunity for someone to click through early on.
See that's like not quite halfway through the video,
but we don't want to wait for them to watch the entire video to click through.
So give them that opportunity, uh, at least once before the main,
the final call to action.
Click shop now to grab yourself a pair of these incredible leakproof underwear
over 73
Th All right, so next we're gonna be talking about social proof.
And this is also a, uh, a XX overlay.
Over 73,200 women are loving design comfort leak proof panties
I love.
All right, so this is obviously social proof. If we,
if you can mention that, show a lot of different people using it, you know,
grids and, um, collages.
This is going to really build up the hype and the excitement, um,
build trust. That's what we're after here.
73,200 women are loving design comfort leak proof panties.
And one thing you'll notice here is that I'm, I'm,
I'm keeping the c t a arrow over here on the left,
kind of like throughout the rest of the video,
just so that they know that they can click over here. Very important. I love
Wearing these under my clothes.
I don't have to worry about a big bulky pad anymore.
I feel super protected all day.
Okay, perfect. So I have three different U G C testimonials here that, you know,
we've shot in the past, but I'm only,
I'm only including ones that are specific to a particular feature or pain
point. 'cause that's really what it comes down to.
It's like you don't want them all saying the same thing.
You want them to be saying different things that, um,
other people can resonate with.
And so you want to kind of like handle some of those objections through your U G
C or through your testimonials.
I,
So next one, and I'm also summarizing what she's saying on the left side,
fits like regular panties, no more bulk, no more bulky pads. Um, I think that's,
that's also another opportunity for them to kind of just like subconsciously
take it all in super
Protected all day. I
Can wear these with anything. No leaks, no lines, no bulk,
nothing. They're perfect.
All right, so that's testimonial number, number two. You know,
she's talking about the bulk making, uh, feeling secure about it.
And what I love about these leakproof panties is that you can throw 'em in the
washing machine and wear 'em over and over. Most of all,
it just gives me peace of mind. So
Ladies, if you have a little leaky issue like me,
and you're looking for a good panty, these panties are discreet, comfortable,
and they keep you protected.
Awesome. So that is the U G C mashup section. All right?
And as you can tell, you know, it's a very simple sequence.
We have that C t a, we have, um, the, the benefits,
um,
alongside the U G C and we have the actual testimonial happening, right?
Um, like I said, the intention here is to just get them to click at this point.
So we, because we've introduced the, introduced the, the product already,
so they already know we've introduced the C T A.
Now let's just get them to click through. All right,
so let's move on to the next final sections.
Provide the solution and the results
Have peace of mind and the confidence,
knowing you're protected from accidents anytime or anywhere,
even from coughs or sneezes.
No more stains and constant laundry. Best of all these panty.
So yeah, let's just go back here really quick. Um,
so providing the solution and the results, like, let me just write this down.
Reiterate
benefits of your product or service. Okay?
So, you know, we watched the U G C, what's in their mind.
We just kind of want to refresh their, their mind of why this is a,
a good option.
Have peace of mind and the confidence knowing you're protected from accidents
anytime or anywhere.
Also,
another opportunity to keyword stuff.
Some of those trigger words, some of those words that they're looking for in,
in, in the product. Peace of mind, confidence protected.
These are all things that, you know,
after reading through hundreds or not thousands of reviews that you know,
this is what people care about.
So if you can kind of already plant that into their subconscious, then you're,
you're gonna win. They'll be
Protected from accidents anytime or anywhere, even from coughs or sneezes.
No more stains and constant laundry. Best of all,
these panties are machine washable and will last you for years to come. Ladies,
end the frustration.
All right, so that is the, the solution. Um,
pretty straightforward, right? I'm using grids again. Um,
I'm show showcasing the pain points here, um,
showing a little bit of the features. Lastly, we have the pain point reminder
And the frustration and embarrassment and feel confident again with design,
comfort, leak, proof, panties.
And then boom, we have our, our final call to action. Okay? So
this call to action, it's kind of ugly, but it is what it is. Uh, there's,
there's urgency here and scarcity. Um, this is,
we're using the timer, the ads arex timer and the ads Arex, C T A and the arrow.
There's a lot of layers here. And, um,
I think it's really smart to add timers on YouTube ads.
I think the mostly just affiliates do this,
and so you kind of give people a reason to click.
It's like you have the timer going on, it feels like time is running out. Um,
and so you want to kind of give them the opportunity if they haven't clicked,
it's like, okay, you got 10 seconds to click, this is your last chance. Um,
another thing too is including your offer in there, if you,
if you have some sort of buy one get one free or get something percentage off,
like, make sure to include that in,
in there as an incentive for them to click through.
And that is the entire video. All right,
so going back to this, we, um,
you know, we did, shoot, shoot, I'm sorry, we didn't,
I didn't shoot this ad specifically for YouTube.
I took previous footage and turned it into a
YouTube ad. So, uh,
I was just gonna show you really quick the other videos that
we've, that we've shot. Uh, here we go,
and let's just sort by views. So yeah, that one got 1.7 million. Uh,
there's one underneath it for, um,
1.2 million and then, you know, a couple hundred thousand for these ones.
But basically what happened was like, um,
I couldn't scale it anymore because the, the ad account got some issues,
but we got it resolved. But now these are starting to run again. And so
whatever offer you're running this, um, this,
this particular sequence can work for you.
You can rearrange some of the ending ones, but I think all,
ultimately the main ones that matter the most is your like,
pattern interrupt or scroll stopper, what's in it for them pain points,
new opportunity, pretty much up to like the c t a,
that first c t a, you have to have that sequence in place,
okay? And then afterwards you can mix it up with like social proof or whatever.
And, you know, this could be, um, this could be,
what's it called, shot in a different way, right?
Right now I'm using a mashup of clips, but it could be a spokesperson, right?
It could be a spokesperson, it could be a U G C. Um,
there's so many different formats that you can use and apply this to,
but like I said, again, it's about the script, it's about the sequencing,
and it's about embedding those keywords and pain points that like the consumer
already knows about and thinks about. Um, you know, and, and it's,
and having that like one, one mechanism, um, I know V Shred,
and I'll maybe just break this down in a different video, but v Shred,
if you've seen 'em on YouTube, like they, they try to like debunk stuff.
It's like if you, if you do cardio, like you're,
you're not gonna get any results losing weight and here's why. You know?
So there is some sort of payoff, um, watching the video.
So that's kind of what we're after here on YouTube is like, okay,
what's the payoff? How do I get them curious to watch?
And yeah, and how do I get them to click? Those are the object, uh, objectives.
Anyways, guys, I hope you, um, found this one helpful. I will do some more,
uh, more training in the future, but thanks for watching.